[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen.
Boys and girls.
Welcome to the greatest show on earth.
The Love, Damini Fair Ground is
officially open for business.
You are kindly encouraged to scream,
yell and shout as loud as you can.
Be prepared to have
the best night of your life.
Give it up for the legendary Outsiders!
["Gbona" playing]
[cheering]
London!
[crowd cheering]
Champion!
Everybody say, "Champion!"
[crowd cheers]
Champion!
- [music ends]
- [laughing]
[crowd cheering]
Man.
This is so amazing, man.
Words cannot begin to describe
my feelings and emotions right now.
[crowd cheering]
Standing here
in front of all of you today, man,
there's nothing else I've dreamed of more.
So what we're gonna do now,
since we're in the stadium,
is we're gonna start from the beginning
of this journey.
So, each and every one of you
who has been there for me
from the beginning of this journey
till this day,
I wanna see your hands up like this.
["Soke" playing]
All my day ones in the building.
Everybody!
Everybody say, "Burna!"
[crowd] Burna!
Bounce with me, bounce with me!
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
["Jagele" playing]
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
Ladies!
[crowd cheers]
["Gwarn" playing]
London!
[crowd cheers]
[music ends]
["Secret" playing]
[Burna Boy] I need you guys to help me out
with this song right here. Let's go!
Sing!
- [music ends]
- How you feeling?
Hey, hands up if you heard my new shit,
the shit I just dropped yesterday.
[crowd cheering]
Right, we gonna try that shit out.
["Sittin' On Top Of The World" playing]
- Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
- [music ends]
- Okay.
- [crowd cheering]
Right now, before we drop this next shit,
I need everybody's hands up.
Everyone.
Everyone. Everyone.
London!
[crowd cheering]
This shit looks so fucking beautiful, man.
["For My Hand" playing]
Wave. Wave.
Wave.
Help me out, London.
[laughing]
[music ends]
["Location" playing]
[crowd cheering, screaming]
[Burna Boy] Probation!
[Dave] How long?
[Burna Boy] What?
Wave.
Jump! Jump!
[music ends]
Make some noise for my brother Dave, yeah.
- [crowd cheering]
- Fucking legend, man.
London, I love you!
[Burna Boy] London.
Man...
Just the other day, man,
I was just...
[quoting "Friendly" lyrics]
[rapper quoting "Friendly" lyrics]
[crowd cheering]
[crowd screaming]
London, make some fucking noise for J Hus!
[crowd cheering]
["Play Play" playing]
[music ends]
[crowd cheers]
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Hey, it's crazy!
[speaking indistinctly]
Everybody say, "Burna!
- We wanna party!"
- [crowd] We wanna party!
["On The Low" playing]
Everybody-- everybody sing!
Sing!
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
Everybody good?
["Collateral Damage" playing]
Everybody,
put one fist up in the air like this!
I wanna see the whole building
with their fists up like this!
Up there, I can't see your fist!
Up there, up there, up there!
Now blow that shit!
Pump your fists in the air!
[music ends]
[crowd cheers]
[singing "Bank On It"]
["Bank On It" playing]
London, I need your help with this one!
Sing that shit!
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
I need all the lights in the building.
If you have a phone, put the lights on.
If you have a torchlight,
put that shit on.
Whatever kind of light,
just put that shit on.
["Alone" playing]
[crowd cheering]
Make some noise for Bishop, man.
The greatest saxophonist on earth.
Make some noise for my band,
The Outsiders,
the greatest band on earth.
[crowd cheering]
They've been riding with me
for the last eight, nine years now.
So, we're pretty much family and shit.
London.
- [music stops]
- We're gonna try this one last time.
And you guys are gonna be my choir.
So, I don't need you guys right now.
It goes like this.
[crowd cheers]
["Dangote" playing]
This one's to all my hustlers
in the building.
Everyone that does what they have to do
to put food on the table.
Everyone that did what they had to do
to be here today.
I appreciate you.
Sing!
[music ends]
[cheering]
It's a real special night tonight.
We gonna keep it that way.
["Real Life" playing]
Lights! Lights!
[screaming, cheering]
[Burna Boy] Sing!
Wave.
[music ends]
That's it, brother.
[crowd cheering]
Hey, Mike, what we got for them, man?
- ["Own It" playing]
- [Burna Boy] Flip that.
One, two.
- One, two, three. Hey, London!
- [Burna Boy] Let's go!
Yeah! Yeah!
[Stormzy] All right!
All right!
One! Two! Yeah!
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
Make some noise for Big fucking Mike, man.
Storm's in the building. The legend, man.
[Burna Boy] Love you, nigga.
Ladies!
["Toni-Ann Singh" playing]
- Oi!
- [Burna Boy] Oi!
Say "Bumbaclot"!
Say "Oi-oi"!
All you Jamaicans, put your hands up!
Yeah.
Oi-oi!
- Hands up! Hands up!
- Jump! Jump! Jump!
[Popcaan] Put your hands up!
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
[music ends]
Make some noise for the Unruly Boss.
[crowd cheering]
["Different Size" playing]
Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn!
Everybody say, "Burna!
We wanna burn party!"
[crowd] Burna! We wanna party!
[music ends]
["Sungba" playing]
Lights on! Lights on! Lights on!
Lights on! Lights on!
[The Outsiders]
Everyone lighten this place.
Everyone in the building.
I wanna see every fucking light.
Now follow me!
Go low!
Go low, go low, go low,
go low, go low, go low, go low.
Whoa!
[crowd cheering]
["Jerusalema" playing]
I need you to sing this shit
at the top of your lungs! Let's go!
I can't hear you!
[music ends]
- [crowd cheering]
- ["Anybody" plays]
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
[The Outsiders] Hey!
Hey!
- Put your hands up!
- Hey!
- [Du-Wayne] Put your hands up!
["Kilometre" playing]
Sing!
This side alone!
All the way back there!
All right. This side, this side.
All the way at the top!
All the way in the back! And up there!
All the way in the back!
[crowd cheering]
[music ends]
["Killing Dem" playing]
Clap! Clap! Clap!
Everybody, clap your hands like this!
Come on!
[music ends]
[crowd cheering]
Everybody say, "Burna!"
[crowd] Burna!
Burna!
[music ends]
- [crowd cheering]
- [laughs]
Everybody good?
[crowd cheering] Yeah!
Yeah, man.
Africa is in the stadium tonight, man.
The whole world
is in the stadium tonight, man.
[crowd cheering]
[singing "It's Plenty"]
London!
["It's Plenty" playing]
I need you guys to sing this shit
at the top of your lungs with the drums.
One more time!
[crowd cheering]
[music ends]
Man.
That was so amazing, man.
Hold on. Hold on.
I need all the lights
in the building once again, man.
Phone lights. Any kind of light.
Pom-pom light.
MD.
["Ye" playing]
[crowd cheering]
[music ends]
MD, MD, MD.
Where did all my lights go?
[crowd cheering]
Don't take the lights away.
I need them lights there.
MD.
["Ye" playing]
London!
[crowd cheering]
[crowd singing]
One more time!
[crowd cheering]
[music ends]
[Burna Boy] Man.
Man. This is such a blessing for me, man.
But at the same time, I told them.
I told them this was gonna happen
right from the beginning.
You understand?
I told them I'm a genius.
I had to show them what the reason is.
100,000 hands where the ceiling is.
[crowd cheering]
I told them I'm the highest.
With the drip I'm the flyest.
100,000 hands where the sky is.
MD!
["Last, Last" playing]
[crowd cheering]
Sing!
I need you to repeat after me.
Just do it like I do.
- Are you ready?
- [cheering]
Okay.
What?
I love you, London!
[crowd cheering]
[music ends]
[screams] You can't beat that!
[cheering continues]